[{
        "id": "0",
        "question": "Name the spell Hermione uses to fix Harry's glasses?",
        "options": [
            "Oculus Reparo",
            "Avada Kadavra",
            "Petrificus Totalus",
            "Crucio"
        ],
        "correct": "Oculus Reparo"
    },
    {
        "id": "1",
        "question": "What is the name of the Weasleys old owl?",
        "options": [
            "Artemis",
            "Hedvig",
            "Errol",
            "Brodwin"
        ],
        "correct": "Errol"

    },
    {
        "id": "2",
        "question": "Viktor Krum is selected by the Goblet of Fire as a Triwizard champion for which school?",
        "options": [
            "Beauxbatons Academy of Magic",
            "Durmstrang Institute",
            "Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry",
            "Mahoutokoro School of Magic"
        ],
        "correct": "Durmstrang Institute"

    },
    {
        "id": "3",
        "question": "Who instructs the Hogwarts suits of armour to defend the castle, using 'Piertotum Locomotor', during the battle of Hogwarts",
        "options": [
            "Professor Slughorn",
            "Professor Trelawny",
            "Professor Snape",
            "Professor McGonagall"
        ],
        "correct": "Professor McGonagall"

    },
    {
        "id": "4",
        "question": "What creature threatens Harry, Ron and Hermione at Gringotts?",
        "options": [
            "A Dragon",
            "A Spider",
            "A Troll",
            "A Dementor"
        ],
        "correct": "A Dragon"

    },
    {
        "id": "5",
        "question": "What is Professor Dumbledore's full name?",
        "options": [
            "Peter Albus Brian Argus Dumbledore",
            "Brian Horace Percival Albus Dumbledore",
            "Albus Peter Horace Argus Dumbledore",
            "Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore"
        ],
        "correct": "Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore"

    },
    {
        "id": "6",
        "question": "How long do the champions have to complete the second task of the Triwizard Tournament?",
        "options": [
            "A day",
            "Twelve hours",
            "Two hours",
            "An hour"
        ],
        "correct": "An hour"

    },
    {
        "id": "7",
        "question": "How many players are on a Quidditch team?",
        "options": [
            "Five",
            "Seven",
            "Nine",
            "Eleven"
        ],
        "correct": "Seven"

    },
    {
        "id": "8",
        "question": "What is written on Dobbys grave?",
        "options": [
            "Here Lies Dobby, A Free Elf",
            "Here Lies Dobby, A Loyal Servant",
            "Here Lies Dobby, A Loyal Friend",
            "He doesn't get a grave"
        ],
        "correct": "Here Lies Dobby, A Free Elf"

    },
    {
        "id": "9",
        "question": "Who leaves chocolates laced with a love potion on Harry's bed which Ron accidentally eats?",
        "options": [
            "Lavender Brown",
            "Hermione Granger",
            "Luna Lovegood",
            "Romilda Vain"
        ],
        "correct": "Here Lies Dobby, A Free Elf"

    }
]